<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>What you'll find on the farm on Cascina La Cà | La Serradesca Società Agricola</title><link>https://laserradesca.github.io/agrihugo/en/services/</link><description>Recent content in What you'll find on the farm on Cascina La Cà | La Serradesca Società Agricola</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 11:16:38 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://laserradesca.github.io/agrihugo/en/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fresh food, straight from the fields</title><link>https://laserradesca.github.io/agrihugo/en/services/fruit/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 11:16:38 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://laserradesca.github.io/agrihugo/en/services/fruit/</guid><description>We grow what we love, and what works in our local conditions: species and varieties are inspired locally and from our travels around the world.
All of our fresh produce is grown to be hand-picked in the field by us, or directly by you to take home and enjoy: fruit, veg and berries, nuts, aromatic herbs and edible, decorative plants.
Join our newsletter to stay updated on seasonal availability.
Our farming philosophy While we do adopt many organic farming methods, our research and experience has led us to decide against organic certification because we believe that integrating certain conventional farming practices improves the sustainability of our farm, both for the environment, and for us, our neighbours and our customers.</description></item><item><title>Farm Learning</title><link>https://laserradesca.github.io/agrihugo/en/services/farm/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 11:16:38 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://laserradesca.github.io/agrihugo/en/services/farm/</guid><description>From kids to adults, we believe it’s important to stay curious about our surroundings: think about them in creative new ways, have the courage to challenge held opinions, and experiment with what at first may seem strange and difficult.
Our workshops and courses focus on the farming techniques and cultural roots of all our produce, the local wild environment, and agriculture in Bergamo and the world both historically and today. We offer:</description></item><item><title>Our honey and our hives</title><link>https://laserradesca.github.io/agrihugo/en/services/honey/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 11:16:38 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://laserradesca.github.io/agrihugo/en/services/honey/</guid><description>Lauren&amp;rsquo;s greatest passion on the farm, our honey beehives are essential to the whole operation: they pollinate our crops, produce delicious honey, and are an integral part of our educational program. Our thousand flowers honey has a signature touch of chestnut flavour, thanks to the surrounding forest.
Get in touch to sample and order our honey.</description></item><item><title>Our wine and our vineyard</title><link>https://laserradesca.github.io/agrihugo/en/services/wine/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 11:16:38 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://laserradesca.github.io/agrihugo/en/services/wine/</guid><description>We produce three grape varieties particular to the Bergamo region for the production of Bergamasca IGT classified wine. IGT stands for Indicazione Geografica Tipica, and you can read more about what that means here.
Our Moscato Giallo grape is an historical variety for Bergamo winegrowers. This grape is usually cultivated to produce muscat or dessert (passito) wine, but we have chosen a classic, dry winemaking method, obtaining an excellent appetiser, or aperitivo, wine.</description></item></channel></rss>